titantv.com 2017-06-06

# TitanTV - Privacy Policy Page

TitanTV.com Privacy Policy (updated November 13, 2015)

At  **TitanTV, Inc.** we recognize the importance of privacy to users of TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application. This Privacy Policy explains what type of information may be collected from you when you access TitanTV.com or the TitanTV.com Mobile Application and how that information may be used. Please note that this Privacy Policy pertains only to TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application, and is separate and distinct from the privacy policies, end user license agreements, terms or service, or terms of use governing: (a) the web sites, applications and services of TITANTV's clients; (b) the web sites, applications and services that may link to or from the TitanTV.com website or the TitanTV.com Mobile Application; and (c) other TITANTV web sites, applications or services. “TitanTV.com Mobile Application” means the TitanTV.com executable code version of the software provided by TITANTV, including associated documentation and services, designed to run on some mobile devices.

**Gathering of Information**

TITANTV may collect personally-identifying information from TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application for a variety of purposes. Such personally identifying information may include, but is not limited to, your name, address, and e-mail address.

TITANTV may ask you to provide certain personal information when you register for certain features or services included in TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application. TITANTV also may ask you to provide personal information in other limited circumstances specified at the time the information is gathered. Any information that you submit on or through TitanTV.com or the TitanTV.com Mobile Application may become public.

Like all other Web servers, TITANTV's Web server may automatically create log files for each user who accesses TitanTV.com or the TitanTV.com Mobile Application. These "access logs" may allow TITANTV to make TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application more useful to our users. The access logs may record the identifier provided for your mobile device by your wireless carrier ("carrier identifier"). Otherwise, the access logs do NOT record a user's name, address, e-mail address, credit card numbers, or any other personally-identifying information. Rather, they may contain some or all of the following information:

o   The Internet Protocol Address (IP Address) of the device which downloaded, installed or used the Mobile Application.

o   The date of use.

o   The time of use.

o   The path taken through TitanTV.com or the TitanTV.com Mobile Application.

o   The operating system and device type being used.

o   A list of files downloaded or viewed.

o   The amount of time spent listening to/viewing media files.

o   Any errors encountered.

o   The device’s geographic location.

**Cookies and Other Technologies**

TITANTV may also use 'cookies' to collect information. A cookie is a string of characters that can be written to a file on the user's device when the user accesses TitanTV.com or downloads, installs or uses the TitanTV.com Mobile Application.

TITANTV uses cookies to track users' activity through TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application in order to improve the site, the application architecture, to offer the features that would not be possible without them, to offer third party content, and to recall specific information to save the user time during subsequent use of TitanTV.com or the TitanTV.com Mobile Application. For example, cookies allow TITANTV to remember your (and/or your device’s) location. Interactive features may also use cookies. Our sponsorship service vendors, which serve sponsorship messages onto TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application, and third party vendors that measure and analyze the use of TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application for TITANTV, may also use their own cookies.

TITANTV and the third party vendors that measure and analyze use of TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application for TITANTV also may use web beacons, alone or in conjunction with cookies, to help compile information about and facilitate usage of TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application. A web beacon is an electronic image, also known as a single-pixel (1x1) or clear .gif, which can be used to recognize certain information on your device, such as cookies, the time and date of your actions within TitanTV.com or the TitanTV.com Mobile Application, and a description of where content is placed. We may use web beacons on TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application from time to time for this and other purposes.

**Use of Information**

TITANTV may use personally-identifying information to:

o   manage or administer TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application;

o   optimize or customize the delivery of advertising or content to you and other users of TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application;

o   respond to user messages;

o   list device location (city, state and/or country) information;

o   contact users for an online survey;

o   send e-mail newsletters and other communications, including marketing and promotional communications, from TITANTV, TITANTV sponsors, TITANTV suppliers, TITANTV licensors, and TITANTV clients to users;

o   other internal TITANTV or TITANTV client purposes; and/or

o   for other purposes specified at the time the information is gathered.

Excluding information provided by the user, which may become public as discussed above, personally-identifying information collected by TITANTV may be given to the following third parties:

o    TITANTV’s clients, suppliers, licensors, advertising partners, and service vendors; and

o    other third parties when you specifically consent to such distribution (such as the disclosure of your name to a friend when you email, send via SMS or text message, or otherwise share a story to that friend).

In these circumstances, the information is provided to a third party for the purposes of

o   delivering TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application and any associated service, advertising, or content to you;

o   delivering communications from TITANTV or TITANTV clients, suppliers, licensors, advertising partners or service vendors;

o   providing services for and on behalf of TITANTV; or

o   serving other TITANTV purposes.

TITANTV also may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or with legal process, (b) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application, or (c) protect the personal safety or property of users of TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application, the public or TITANTV and its employees.

If you do not want your personally-identifying information to be collected or used for any of these purposes, please do not provide it and do not access TitanTV.com or download, install or use the TitanTV.com Mobile Application.

**Third-Party Advertising**

We use several third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you access TitanTV.com or when you download, install or use the TitanTV.com Mobile Application. Some of these companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by some of these companies, please [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**Security**

TITANTV has in place what we believe to be appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, no Internet, e-mail or mobile transmission is ever fully secure or error free and TITANTV cannot guarantee that any information will be or remain safe or secure. Because most e-mail and mobile transmissions are not encrypted, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail, SMS or text message, or other mobile transmission.

**Children**

If you are under 13 years of age, please do not access TitanTV.com or download, install or use the TitanTV.com Mobile Application. TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application are not intended for children under 13, and TITANTV will not knowingly collect any information from any children under the age of 13. If we discover that we have collected any personally-identifying information from a child under the age of 13, we will promptly remove that information from our database.

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy Terms**

TITANTV reserves the right to change this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted to this page as soon as reasonably possible, so please check this page periodically. Use of TitanTV.com or the TitanTV.com Mobile Application constitutes consent to any policy then in effect. Please make sure that you read the [TitanTV.com Terms and Conditions of Use](http://titantv.com/terms.aspx) to understand additional terms and conditions which apply to the use of TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application.

**Links to other Sites and Services**

It is important to note that TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application may contain links to other sites, applications and services maintained by third parties that may not follow the same privacy policies as TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application. For instance, clicking or tapping on a sponsorship notice or some third party logos on TitanTV.com or the TitanTV.com Mobile Application will take you to an entirely different site, application or service. These sites, applications and services may use cookies, collect data, and use the data in ways that TitanTV.com or the TitanTV.com Mobile Application would not. TITANTV is not responsible for the privacy practices or any information or materials on these other sites, applications and services. Please visit these sites or applications if you wish to review their privacy policies.

In some cases, TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application may include certain embedded tools provided and controlled by third parties and governed by the terms and policies of the third parties. You should only use these third party tools if you agree to their respective terms and policies.

TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application may include a tool that allows you to sign in using information from your account with a third party service, such as Facebook, Twitter, Google, Yahoo, OpenID, or LinkedIn. Please be aware that those third party services are unrelated to TITANTV, and that your use of the third party services is subject to the terms and policies of those services.

**International User Notice**

For international users, please note that it may be necessary to transfer your information internationally and, in particular, your information may be transferred to and processed in the United States. For residents of the European Union: the data protection and other laws of other countries outside of the European Union may not be as comprehensive as those of the European Union. Please be assured that we take steps to ensure that your privacy is protected as described in this policy. By accessing TitanTV.com or downloading, installing or using the TitanTV.com Mobile Application, you agree to have your information used and transferred to the United States as set forth in this policy. If you access TitanTV.com or download, install or use the TitanTV.com Mobile Application from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of TitanTV.com or the TitanTV.com Mobile Application, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy and the [TitanTV.com Terms and Conditions of Use](http://titantv.com/terms.aspx), you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

**In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy**

In the event that TITANTV, TitanTV.com or the TitanTV.com Mobile Application business is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

**Questions**

If you have any questions or comments concerning our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [legal@TitanTV.com](mailto:legal@TitanTV.com).

Last Updated: November 13, 2015
